Guide to the Stanford Video Master Recordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Video master recordings
1977-2010
V0329
Stanford Video.
19 Linear feet
and 176 gigabytes
Collection contains master recordings in a variety of formats, primarily of films related to Stanford events and people, with a few film-to-tape transfers of earlier sources.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Reformatting is necessary for physical media; consult the University Archivist for access.
Description of the Collection
The collection contains master recordings in a variety of formats, primarily of films related to Stanford events and people, with a few film-to-tape transfers of earlier sources.
Access Terms
Stanford Video.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Videorecordings, Accession ARCH-2006-294
  - Speaking of Stanford. [V042], 10-27-1988; 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 1)
  - Terman Dedication, 10-6-1977; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 1)
  - Mitterrand Visit to CIS (1 of 2), Large Beta. [V103], 3-26-1984 (Box 1)
  - Preventing and Managing Stress, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 1)
  - Preventing and Managing Computer Related Injuries, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 1)
  - Alumni Assoc.- Chalk Talk, Stanford Coaches, 4-27-1995; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 1)
  - Marianne Gammon--Bankcard Management School. Stanford B-Roll., 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 1)
  - Breast Cancer Risks- What can you do about it?, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 1)
  - Alumni Assoc.- Frosh on the Farm, First Impression of Stanford, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 1)
  - Computer Museum History Center., 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 1)
  - #3 Nobel Awards Banquet, 1996 Dec 10; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 2)
  - #6 Nobel Awards Opening Ceremonies, 1996 Dec 10; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 2)
  - Sterling's Inauguration. [V031], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 2)
  - Best of Fred Terman- Interview., 1982; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 2)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve--An Island of Discovery. [V200], 1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam Sm) (Box 2)
  - Wallace Sterling Inauguration, film-to-tape transfer, 9-24-1949; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 2)
  - Grapes in the 90s- Serving Grapes at Stanford, 11-29-1985; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - Bill Gates in Conversation with John Hennessy, 4-25-2002; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - Earthquakes in the Holy Land., 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - Vaclav Havel Addresses Stanford Law School., 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - Today Show w/ Barry bonds Interview, 10-11-2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 3)
  - Video Fillers- Jericho Fault, Super-Conductivity, Jasper Ridge (Box 3)
  - Stanford in Autumn [V035], 3-23-1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 3)
  - University Overview for Prospective Applicants, 4-19-1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 4)
  - ASSU Lecture Series- Shirley Chisholm [V112], 1-15-1986; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 4)
  - Lecture Series- Alex Haley, 3-15-1986; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 4)
  - This is Supri., 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 4)
  - Cantor Arts Center, [V194], 1-12-1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 4)
  - Celebration of a Presidency- The Gerhard Casper Years, 1992-2000. [V280], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 4)
  - Haas Center- Reflections on the 1st 15 Years, Oct 2000; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Travel Clip- "Northwest Passage.", 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 4)
  - SU 50th Anniv. Celebration/Med Center Construction, 9-24-1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 4)
  - HOS/50th Anniversary Celebration., 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 5)
  - Hoover Tower 50th Anniv. Rededication, 7-18-1991; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Earthquake Rebuilding- Kile Ozier Slide Show, 6-4-90; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 6)
  - SU Earthquake Damage [V054.2], 10-19-1989; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 6)
  - To Touch History: Gorbachev at Stanford. [V059], 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 7)
  - HumBio 4B 9AM, Dimensions of Environmental Destruction- Donald Kennedy, 5-15-89. [V256.335 in box 25], 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 7)
  - President Kennedy Roast., 5-18-1992; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 7)
  - SU Public Affairs- Donald Kennedy Statement/Q&A, 7-29-1991; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 7)
  - SU Public Affairs- Donald Kennedy Statement/Q&A, 7-30-1991; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 7)
  - Stanford Climate Change Video News Release, 11-20-2002; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 7)
  - The Stanford Experience [V015], 1983; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 7)
  - Chalk Talk 1 & 2, Stanford Coaches., film reel (35mm) (Box 8)
  - MLK Edit, Victor Walker. 1-inch reel. [could be V075, V101, or something else] (Box 8)
  - Gorbachev 1-inch reel. [V089], June 1990 (Box 8)
  - Stanford Views. [V195], 7-12-1993; 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 8)
  - Donald Kennedy and George Hume-Stanford at the Crossroads. [VHS copy in SC261], 11-18-1991; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 8)
  - Kennedy Farewell Party, 6-11-1992; 2 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 8)
  - 20/20 Shot of Donald Kennedy [V092], 1-30-1991; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 8)
  - Stanford New President Announcement Prof. John Hennessy, 4-3-2000; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 9)
  - Campus Confessions, 11-25-1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 9)
  - Preventing and Managing Back Pain, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 9)
  - Annual Meeting of the Academic Council, 4-18-2002; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 9)
  - Stanford Media Works, 5-26-2000; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 9)
  - Overseas Studies at 40, 1998 Sep; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 9)
  - Stanford Traffic, 9-2-1997; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SM) (Box 9)
  - Good and Evil. [V087], 12-1-1993; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam-SP L) (Box 10)
  - YAHOO! Jerry and Dave's Excellent Venture. [V216], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 10)
  - Healthcare- Putting Cancer in Perspective: Diagnosis, 1992 Jun 8; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 10)
  - Healthcare- Putting Cancer in Perspective: Treatment, 1992 Jun 8; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 10)
  - Healthcare- Putting Cancer in Perspective: Support, 1992 Jun 8; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 10)
  - Healthcare- Putting Cancer in Perspective: The Future, 1992 Jun 8; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 10)
  - Charles Stein Last Statistics Lecture at Sequoia Hall, 3-19-1996; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 10)
  - Irvine Grant., 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 10)
  - Good & Evil. [V087], 12-1-1993; 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 11)
  - Stockdale Triumphs: A Return to Vietnam., film reel (35mm) (Box 11)
  - Stanford Views, Trustees Demo, ABC Footage, 10-13-1993; 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 11)
  - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Overview and Intro, 10-26-1993; film reel (35mm) (Box 11)
  - Great Teachers, Great Texts #3- Diane Middlebrook- The Poetry of Sylvia Plath and Anne Sexton. 2 parts, March 1993; 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 12)
  - Great Teachers, Great Texts/Packer, Faulkner, 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 12)
  - Earthquakes in the Holy Land., film reel (35mm) (Box 12)
  - Stanford in its 2nd Century- Address by Pres. Donald Kennedy, 4-5-1990; film reel (35mm) (Box 12)
  - Alex Haley, 3-5-1986; film reel (35mm) (Box 13)
  - Commencement Address- Stephen Carter. [V141], 1994; 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 13)
  - Commencement, highlights of Baccalaureate Service and Senior Class Day Luncheon. [V141 probably], 1994; 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 13)
  - Winter One Acts, Waiting for Godot and Connection Down. (Box 13)
  - Museum Master, CSL1 Master. (Box 14)
  - Stanford Public Affairs- Donald Kennedy Statement/Q&A, 7-29-1991; film reel (35mm) (Box 14)
- Videorecordings, Accession ARCH-2008-117
  - Milton Friedman / Tom Sowell, 2004 Apr 7; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Democracy Now at Stanford, 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - TCT Conference, Global Entrepreneurs Challenge, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Sons and Daughters, 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Communications. Discovery Channel Canada. Interview with Herbert Clark, 6/11/2002; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 1)
  - Beyond Words. New Tools for the Learning Community. Stanford Learning Lab, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 1)
  - To Touch History: Gorbachev at Stanford, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 1)
  - Shirley Chisholm Lecture Series, Edited Master, 1/15/1986; 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Stockdale Triumphs. A Return to Vietnam, 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Donald Kennedy's Inauguration Tape 1/2, November 1980; 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Donald Kennedy's Inauguration Tape 2/2, November 1980; 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Rodin Sculpture Garden Dedication & Gates of Hell. Edited master [note: no audio], 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Kennedy / Carter visit, 1983 Jul 18; 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Earthquake Damage/Internal Version and SITN class footage, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - The Stanford Archive Pilot. Dub of edited master, 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - The Museum Pilot. Dub from edited master, 6/25/1986; 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Earthquake Damage/Broadcast version, Oct. 19, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Professional Publishing Course. Edited Master, 10/19/1985; Video Reel (Box 1)
  - unidentified, audiotape (DAT) (Box 1)
  - HOS [History of Stanford?]. Mausoleum A.M, 5/18/1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - HOS. Lake Lagunita at dawn, 1998 Jul 16; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - HOS II. KRON-TV A83 [copies of archival footage: MLK speech, Old Union sit-in 1968; 1970 anti-ROTC], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - HOS II. KRON-TV A84 [copies of archival footage: 1970 Old Union; Pitzer resignation/search for a new pres.], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - John Hutchinson discovery. The dinosaur and the chicken, 3/19/2002; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital. Open Heart Baby, 2/21/2002; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Below the Skin dance, Memorial Aud, 2003 Mar 1; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Unlabelled; has business card of Julie Learmond-Criqui of Dell'Oro Group, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Bars & Tone and Extended Stanford Views, 6/23/1994; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Sect. Madeline Albright, tape 1, 10/6/1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Sect. Madeline Albright, Hoover Luncheon, tape 2, 10/6/1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Morrie Doyle, An Uncommon Man, edited master, 11/13/1997; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Linda Meier, An Uncommon Woman, edited master, 2/1/2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Breast Cancer Awareness and Prevention, 1/03/2002; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - The Optimal Diet for Overall Health, 12/28/2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Heart Disease Prevention and Management, 12/27/2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Understanding Menopause, 12/28/2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - Healthy Aging, 2001 Dec 28; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #10 [no label list], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #3 [contents on label], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #4 [contents on label], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #5 [contents on label], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #6 [contents on label], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #7 [contents on label], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #8 [contents on label], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - MVP Digital Compilation Master #9 [contents on label], 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - KRON-TV News Archival [contents on label], 1968-1987; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - KRON-TV News (Kennedy, Casper, Centennial, Multiculturalism), 1990s; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - Forgive for Good, home video version, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 3)
  - Stockdale edit 2, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - William Gates Computer Science Building: Exteriors, students, interiors, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - William Gates Computer Science Building: Exteriors, students, interiors. MASTER., 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford builds for the 21st century, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association new building time lapse, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford - past, present, future; Dan Kirby - open, David Neuman - open/close, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 4)
  - Governor Gray Davis, 10/15/1999; 1 videotape(s) (Hi-8) (Box 4)
  - Stanford archival: political rally, the Challenging Era, the world within, the True Source of Knowledge, 1960s; 1 videotape(s) (Hi-8) (Box 4)
  - MAC, Presidents Welcome & The Difference, 4/30/2004; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 4)
  - Nobel Prize, Osheroff/reception tape 2, 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Nobel Prize, Osheroff/interview tape 3, 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Nobel Prize Ceremony Physics/Osheroff, 12/10/1996; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Nobel Prize Ceremony Osheroff/ reception, ceremony, interview, 12/11/1996; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Visit of His Holiness the Dalai Lama, Memorial Church, Session 1, 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Hoover Uplink, beauty shots, 7/7/1989; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - State of the University Address, President Gerhard Casper, 4/28/1993; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - William Gates Computer Science Building Dedication/Symposium. Master (partial program only) 1/30/1996, 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Stanford University New President Gerhard Casper press conference, 3/18/1992; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Carl Sagan on Human Missions to Mars, April 24, 1993; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Carl Sagan, Is There Intelligent Life on Earth?, April 23, 1993; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Archived shots: S.F. scenic ext.; Gerhard Casper; Campus Building Ext; Stanford Bookstore; Golf Course; Ted Leland; Bill Walsh; Stanford Mall; Stanford Alumni Pics., 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 4)
  - Fillers: PCH - Vision Video; Osheroff Nobel; Stanford Remembers; If She Knew, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 5)
  - Fillers: Hoover Institution; Making a Difference; the ADEPT Interview, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 5)
  - Beauty Shots: Bikers, Church, Quad, Gates etc., September 1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 5)
  - Beauty Shots, 10/13/1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 5)
  - Chanel 151 Beauty Shots, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 5)
  - Admissions BSP Master 16. [Handwritten: Sailing on the Bay] Film-to-Tape transfer, 4/18/2000; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 5)
  - Admissions. Film-to-Tape transfer, 6/6/2000; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam LG) (Box 5)
  - Stanford beauty shots SITN, 1 videotape(s) (Umatic) (Box 5)
  - HOS beauty shots, Roble Hall, 11/16/1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - HOS beauty shots tape #1, 12/17/1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - HOS beauty shots, 12/1/1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Campus Beauty Shots, 10/14/1996; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Beauty Shoots [sic] #2. Jordan Quad to science bldg, GSB Littlefield, Dish/Oval, Palm Drive, Annings, Sunken Diamond, Stadium, November 1995; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Ch. 51 Beauty Shots. Jordan Quad to science bldg, GSB Littlefield, Dish/Oval, Palm Drive, Arrillaga, Sunken Diamond, Stadium, November 28, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - News Service Beauty Shots for 51, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Admissions. BSP. Powwow Assembly, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Recruiting. Helicoptor footage, 10/14/1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Think Again footage [also labeled Stanford CUE promo], 2001 Jun - Aug; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Church beauty shots, Nancy Packer, 2/4/1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Beauty Shots II, also Borland, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Beauty Shots 3. Red roofs, Tile, Nov. 1995; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Ch. 51 Beauty shots. Old Union/Claw/Hoover Tower; Meyer Library; Language Corner; Quad West gate/Hoover Tower; Inner Quad; Arches; Oval from Arches, 11/28/1995; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - HOS. Roble and fall trees, 11/17/1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Stanford B-Roll, 4/14/91; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - History of Stanford. Tape 3, 4/9/1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - SLAC B-roll, 9/20/2003; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - The Learning Lab (B-roll), 10/23/2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Admissions DV Tape 4: Cursha ASB in Hawaii, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Admissions Video, 8/30/2000; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 5)
  - Ch. 51 beauty shots. Red roods, tile, 11/28/1995; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - Stanford beauty shots Tape #2, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - Beauty Shoots [sic] #1. Old Union/Claw/Hoover Tower; Meyer Library; Language Corner; Quad West gate/Hoover Tower; Inner Quad/Church; Arches; Oval from Arches, November 1995, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - History of Stanford beauty shots Tape 1, 11/25/1997; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - History of Stanford, beauty shots, fence/poppies, 3/11/1999; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - History of Stanford, beauty shots Tape #3, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - Stanford beauty shots, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - JRBP. Tape #1 Beauty shots spring flowers, 4/12/1998; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - Admission Video, beauty shots, July 2000; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - Stanford Alumni Association "Stanford Video" Open, 9/29/1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - Stanford CUE project / Think Again Raw footage, August 2001; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam) (Box 6)
  - Church beauty shots, Nancy Packer, 2/4/1999; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Passages of Martin Luther King Jr. Directed by Victor Leo Walker II, written by Clay Carson, #2052; film reel (35mm)
  - Great Teachers, Great Text #3--Diane Middlebrook. The Poetry of Sylvia Plath and Anne Sexton. Edited Master. March 1993, #2058; film reel (35mm)
- Dalai Lama visit, 2010 Oct 14-15; Accession ARCH-2010-129
  - Videorecordings
    - Dalai Lama, Maples Pavilion, preview, 2010 Oct 14; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 1)
    - Dalai Lama, Maples Pavilion, 2010 Oct 14; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 1)
    - Dalai Lama, Maples Pavilion, 2010 Oct 14; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
    - Dalai Lama, Memorial Church program, 2010 Oct 14; 1 optical disc(s) (XDCAM) (Box 1)
    - Dalai Lama, Memorial Auditorium, Session 1, Preview, Tape #1, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 2)
    - Dalai Lama, Memorial Auditorium, Session 1, Program, Tape #1, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 2)
    - Dalai Lama, Memorial Auditorium, Session 2, Preview, Tape #1, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 2)
    - Dalai Lama, Memorial Auditorium, Session 2, Program, Tape #1, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 2)
    - Dalai Lama, Program Master, Session 1, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 2)
    - Dalai Lama, Memorial Auditorium, Session 2, Program, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 2)
    - Dalai Lama, Memorial Auditorium, Session 1, Preview, Tape #2, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 2)
    - Dalai Lama, Session 1, Program, Tape #2, 2010 Oct 15; 1 videotape (Digital Betacam) (Box 2)
  - Computer files
    - Rathbun Lecture, On a Meaningful Life, 2010 Oct 14; 53 gigabyte(s); (187 computer files)
    - Scientific Explorations of Compassion and Altruism, 2010 Oct 14; 90.4 gigabyte(s); (518 computer files)
    - Centrality of Compassion, 32.8 gigabyte(s); (198 computer files)